Guide to the Medical Center Public Relations records, 1913-1999 RG0045
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Medical Center history, 1980-1990; RG0045 Series 6; 6 Linear feet
  This series contains historical files, photographs, press kits, biographical files, and newspaper articles. The material dates from 1980-90. The subjects of this material include Ronald Reagan's shooting, the construction of the Foggy Bottom Metro, Ella Fitzgerald, Medical Follies, match day, nurses, the Medical Center, and Mother Theresa. Box 1 may contain more files than are listed.
  - Historical File on Medical Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press Kits, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Biographical files, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations clippings, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Wire Clips on Reagan Shooting, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - University President Elliott, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Disaster Drills, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - EEG Photos, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Department of Emergency Medicine, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - EMS Week, 10/1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Employee Banquet, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Equipment, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Family Research Center, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Fire Damage, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ella Fitzgerald, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Foggy Bottom Metro Construction, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Follies, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Graduation, 05/1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - GW Medicine, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Alumni, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Medical Education, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - GW Home Care, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Holiday Tea, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Holyfest, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Housekeeping Open House, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Intensive Care Nursery, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - IVF, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Original finding aid does not explain abbreviation
  - Cecil Jacobson Anacephalic Fetus, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Ronald Kaufman, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lab Shots, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - McCarthur Payroll, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Match Day, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Microsopes / Red & White Cells, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Microsurgery, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Mother Theresa, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - National Library of Medicine, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - NBC Baby, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - National Airport Clinic, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Neurosurgery, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Noise Campaign, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Nursery, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Nursing, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Nurses, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Obstetrics / Gynecology, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 3 North: Reunion, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Dr. Dennis O'Leary, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Opthamology, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Patients, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - People--general, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Pharmacy, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Physical Therapy, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Physician Assistant, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Radiology, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Reagan Era Photos, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Rehabilitation, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Research, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Ross Hall Center, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Employee Awards, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Social Services, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Special Police, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Speech Pathology, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Stock Shots, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Surgery Shots, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Schneider & Sons, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fairfax Opportunities Unlimited, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Julie Newhouse, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - District Litho, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - GraphTech Inc., undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Contests, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Image Photographers, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Kelly Girl Services, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - US Express, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Visual Systems, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Furniture Renters of America, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - D & F Furnishings, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Ritz Camera, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Scott Photographs, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Visual Systems, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Ickow, Warvin, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Old Procurement Forms, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Blanket Purchase Agreements, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Blanket Purchase Agreements, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Blanket Purchase Agreements, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Blanket Purchase Agreements, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Video: Treating Common Ailments, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Video: Etud Redd clip, 07/1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Video: Satisfaction Guaranteed, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Video: Growing Older, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Video: Plateletpheresis, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Audio: Emergency Medicine, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Audio: Opening Oncology Symposium, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Audio: Shaffer & Sank [1/2], undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Audio: Shaffer & Sank [2/2], undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Audio: John Larsen, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Audio: Vallery Portnoi, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Audio: Mervyne L. Elgart, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Audio: Hugh Trout, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Audio: Judy Nicklason, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Audio: Allen Ginsberg, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Audio: Dr. Geelhoed, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Audio: Health Call, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Audio: Dr. Larsen, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Audio: Kaleidescope, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Audio: Dr. Schulof, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Audio: Stuart Sotsky, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Audio: John Larsen, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Large Photo: Nurse with Baby, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Large Photo: Cafeteria, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Large Photo: Doctor at Blackboard, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Large Photo: Hospital, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Faculty personnel files, 1960-1991; RG0045 Series 7; 10.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 1, Box 2)
  This series contains faculty personnel files, Edward Renauer chronological files, and house staff files. The material dates from 1960-91.
  Conditions Governing Access
  The records in this series are closed for 75 years from date of record creation.
  - House Staff, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - House Staff, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - House Staff, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - House Staff, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - House Staff, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - House Staff, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - House Staff, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - House Staff, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - House Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - House Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - House Staff, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - House Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - House Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - House Staff, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - House Staff, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - House Staff, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - House Staff, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - House Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Hospital Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - House Staff, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - House Staff, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - House Staff, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - House Staff, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - House Staff, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - House Staff, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Wilner, Steven, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Wilson, Kenneth, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Winchester, Lynn, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Winfrey, Elisha, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wing, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Winnik, Jeffrey, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Winitsky, Ted, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Winkler, Lee, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Winn, Pat, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Winnacker, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Winston, Brad, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Wipplinger, Karl, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Witte, Jeff, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Wittenstein, Fred, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Wyadyka, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Wohlgemuth, Stephen, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Wolf, Alan, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Wolf, Melvin, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Wolfe, Martin, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Wong, David, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wong, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Wong, Wai, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Wongananda, Boondharm, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Woodford, Renee, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Woodland, Mark, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Woodward, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Worsencroft, Helen, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Worthing, Verla, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Wortman, Rick, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Wuith, Marvin, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Wushensky, Curtis, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Wuim, Scott, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Wyman, Jennifer, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Wysocki, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Yackee, Johb, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Yeoh, Hoik, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Youseff, Ali, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Yu, Keun, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Yuiel, Vebbi, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Yousefi, Bijan, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Yu, Keun, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Yutgy, Carl, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Zafar, Lyed, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Zakaira, Galal, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - House Staff Lists, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - House Staff Lists, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - House Staff Turnover, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Terminations, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Early Checkout, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Reappointment, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Original Lists, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - House Staff Turnover, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - New Appointment, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - House Staff Lists, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - House Staff Turnover, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Original Lists, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - New Appointments, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Terminations, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Reappointments, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - G.W.U.M.C. Patent Education Index, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Sineski, Stefan, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Zirin, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Zohni, Sherif, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Zolman, Joseph, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Zorsky, Paul, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Zuckerman, Jonathan, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Zuckerman, Charles, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Zurowski, Robert, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Zweig, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Zwerdling, David, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Zwerner, Alan R., undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Zwetchkenbaum, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Zwiebel, James Andrew, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Zambrano, Eusebio Andres, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Zarzour, Ernest J., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Zedie, Nishat, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Zeitler, Mitchell, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Zelnik, Nathanel, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Zeveney, Jr., Dennis J., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Zielinski, Christopher J., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Zimmerman, Robert D., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Zimmons, Paul, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Kleinman, Bradford A., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Jocobs, Ronald, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Berman, Michael L., undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Barletta, Arthur P., undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Warren, Herrick S., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Warsof, Steven L., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Wasserman, Alan G., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Wasserman, Gary, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Waterman, Daniel H., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Watson, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Watson, Susan P., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Wayne, Eli R., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Wayner, Robert F., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Weaver, James M., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Webb, Eldon, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Weddle, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Weeks, Byron Thomas, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Weglicki, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Weinberg, Stephen A., undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Weinberger, Daniel, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Weiner, Daniel, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Weiner, Jay, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Weiner, Neil, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Weiner, Paul L., undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Weinfeld, Robert H., undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Weingold, Matthew A., undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Weinstein, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Weinstein, Zelig, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Weintraub, Joel, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Weisbuch, Jonathan B., undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Weiss, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Weiss, Richard, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Weisshaar, Paul, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Weisz, Alice, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Weithorn, Lois, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Weitz, John T., undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Wellman, Abby, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Welsh, Francis P., undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Welsh, Laura, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Welsing, Frances, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Wenger, Francis L., undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Wenzel, Marc, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Werschler, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Wertheim, Ray A., undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Wescoe, Sybil, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Wescott, John W., undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Wessel, Hildegard, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Wesselhoeff, Conrad W., undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - West, John C., undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Westbrook, Suzanne, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Westbrook, Thomas, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Whateley, Brad, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Whately, Elizabeth, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Wheeler, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Wherry, David C., undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Whipple, George A., undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - White, Austin E., undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - White, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - White, George E., undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - White, Greg, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - White, Inez J., undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - White, Jon, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - White, Jonathan, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - White, Neville, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - White, Patience, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - White, Robert S., undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - White, Samuel E., undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - White, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Whitehead, Roger D., undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Whitfield, Peter, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Whye, DePriest, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Wickramasekaran, Rajasekaran, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Weider, Sheldon, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Wigton, Roger B., undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Wilber, Stewart A., undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Wilde, Ralph C., undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Wilkenfeld, Morris J., undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Wilhite, Ann C. O'Brien, undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Wilkes, John D., undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Willeford, Kenneth, undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Willen, Jon F., undated (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Williams, Ann B., undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Williams, Barbara, undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Williams, Bessie K., undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Williams, Daniel, undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Williams, David E., undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Williams, Elizabeth, undated (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Williams, Frederick L., undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Williams, John F., undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Williams, Polly Tweed, undated (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Williams, Robert Edwin, undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Williamson, Harold G., undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Willey, Shawna, undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Willis, Arnold, undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Chinese Restaurant Syndrome, undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - van Breda, Arina, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Vance, John C., undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Van Der Lubbe, Nena E., undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Vanderveen, James L., undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Van Elswyk, James, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Van Oordt, Christine E., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Van Horn-Haigler, Denise, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Vankai, Ruth A., undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Van Leeuwen, Linda, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Van Nice, Paul, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Van Veen, William J., undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Van Wagenen, Nan C., undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Vaum, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Veeder, Michael, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Viehmeyer, Judith, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Velaj, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Veloso, Aniceta R., undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Veluri, Ravi K., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Venable, Josef G., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Vendrell, Michael J., undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Venezia, Donna, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Venkataramani, T.K., undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Venkatesan, Ranganathan, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Venkatesh, Hoskote, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Vera, Zakauddin, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Verde, Rachael, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Vergara, Alfonso I., undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Verghese, Susan, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Verma, Anil, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Vern, Boris, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Vernaglione, Elia, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Vernick, David M., undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Vershel, Genevieve, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Verville, Edward G., undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Viciana, Enrique, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Vidal, Jesus, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Viener, Robert S., undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Vilasi, Vincent S., undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Vilches, Ricardo, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Vilinskas, Juliet, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Villaroman, Isabelo R., undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Villarreal, Luis G., undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Villavicendio, Olmedo, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Vincenty, Claudio, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Vinh, Lan Vien, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Vinis, Lawrence, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Virmani, Renu, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Virnelli, Frank R., undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Vlalukin, Lillian, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Voell, James W., undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Vogeney, James W., undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - von Albertini, Beat, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - von der Schmidt, III, Edward, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Von Hippel, Josephine, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Von Hoffmann, Mary, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Voss, Stephen, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Wacker, Warren E., undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Waddill, Jr., William B., undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Wadhwa, Kamal P., undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Wagner, Ernest A., undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Wagner, Timothy, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Wald, Lawrence M., undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Waldrop, Francis N., undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Walerstein, Steven, undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Walker, Jr., L.G., undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Walker, Robert, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Walker, Thomas F., undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Wall, Haven N., undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Walkey, Marilyn, undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Wallace, William D., undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Wallace, Duncan S., undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Wallace, Marsha T., undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Wallace, Charles H., undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Walsh, Christopher, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Walsh, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Walter, Katharine M., undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Walter, Robert, undated (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Walters, Edward W., undated (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Waltman, Allen, undated (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Wand, Gary, undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Wang, Elaine, undated (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Wang, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Wanicur, David M., undated (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Wanke, Christine, undated (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Warchol, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Ward, Kenneth, undated (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Ward, Kenneth G., undated (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Ward, Kimber A., undated (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Ward, Mary D., undated (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Wargotz, Eric S., undated (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Warkentin, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - L.T. Bowles, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - L.T. Bowles, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - September Chron. Files for EJR, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chron. Files for EJR, 08/1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Chron. Files for EJR, 07/1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chron. - EJR, 06/1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Chron File for EJR, 05/1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Chron Files for EJR, 04/1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chron Files for EJR, 02/1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Chron Files for EJR, 12/1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chron Files for EJR, 03/1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chron Files for EJR, 01/1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File December, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File November, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File October 1984, 10/1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File September 1984, 09/1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File August 1984, 08/1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File July 1984, 07/1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Renauer, 06/1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - EJR, 05/1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - EJR Chron File, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - EJR Chron File, 03/1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File Februrary 1984, 02/1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File, 04/01/1983 --05/31/1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File, 10/01/1983 --11/31/1983 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Ed Renauer's Chron File, 08/01/1983 --09/31/1983 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Fund Sheets, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Fund Sheets3, 02/01/1983 --03/31/1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Fund Sheets, 12/01/1982 --01/31/1983 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Fund Sheets, 07/01/1982 --09/30/1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Burns Clinic Photographs, 1913-1981; RG0045 Series 8; 5 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 5, Box 10, Box 9)
  This series contains photographs, negatives and contact sheets. The material dates from 1913-81. Subjects of these images include alumni weekend, dedication of Ross Hall, Eugene Meyer Pavilion, hospital, nurses home Everglades Hall, women's board, medical school, Foggy Bottom Metro opening, teaching, and staff.
  - Adams Morgan Clinic, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes background information and a summary on the new health clinic
  - Alumni Christmas party, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes an article
  - Alumni Luncheon, 11/22/1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Luncheon, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Includes article "Medical Alumni Hear Space Expert"
  - Alumni Luncheon, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Includes article "A Cork Anatomist Returns a Visit"
  - Alumni Weekend, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Weekend and Scientific Sessions, 05/1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Weekend, Opthamology post-graduate course [1/2], 05/1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)